A Guide to the Papers of Mason C. Andrews 1932-1997
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
The Papers of Mason C. Andrews 1932-1997
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
MG 62
22.5 linear feet, 38 Hollinger document cases.
Administrative Information
Access
Open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dr. Mason C. Andrews, October 1998
Biographical/Historical Information
Mason C. Andrews was born in Norfolk, Virginia in 1919. He graduated from Maury High School, and later received his Bachelor's degree in Chemistry from Princeton and his M.D. from John's Hopkins University. He specialized in obstetrics and gynecology and completed his residency training at Johns Hopkins as well. Andrews then began a successful ob/gyn private practice in Norfolk in 1950. Additionally, Dr. Andrews taught Obstetrics and Gynecology at Johns Hopkins University and later at Eastern Virginia Medical School.
Andrews' community service began during the 1950's with service on the Norfolk Chamber of Commerce and the Health Welfare and Recreation Planning Council. While serving as president of the Norfolk County Medical Society, Andrews appointed a bipartisan committee to study the need for a medical school in the area. The study was able to convince the Virginia General Assembly of the need for a new medical school. In 1964 the Eastern Virginia Medical Center authority was formed with the charge of developing the new medical school. Andrews served as the chairman of the authority from 1964-1970. Under his leadership a medical center complex was built in an area that has once been slums. The medical complex now consists of Eastern Virginia Medical School (EVMS), Norfolk General Hospital, Medical Tower, Public Health Department, Children's Hospital of the King's Daughters and Tidewater Rehabilitation Institute. In addition, as chairman of the Department of Obstetrics and Gynecology at EVMS Andrews was instrumental in bringing the team of Drs. Howard and Georgeanna Jones to Norfolk. The Drs. Jones specialized in treating infertility problems. In 1981 they brought notoriety to Norfolk with the role they played in the first successful birth, in the United States, of a baby conceived by in-vitro fertilization. With the success of the in-vitro fertilization program the Jones Institute for Reproductive Medicine was founded in 1983.
Andrews also served on the Norfolk City Council from 1974 to 2000 and as the city's mayor from 1992 to 1994. During his tenure on the council he was instrumental in the redevelopment of the downtown waterfront. Andrews introduced the developer of Baltimore's Inner Harbor, James Rouse, to Norfolk. Rouse designed the Waterside Festival Marketplace for the Norfolk waterfront. Other downtown projects promoted by Andrews included Nauticus, the Norfolk campus of Tidewater Community College, and the MacArthur Center Mall. Mason Andrews declined to run for re-election to city council in 2000.
Scope and Content Information
The papers of Mason C. Andrews date from 1932 to 1997. The collection includes correspondence related to personal, business and city issues; photographs; medical articles; newspaper clippings; architectural drawings; 16mm film reels; reports; and miscellaneous materials. The bulk of the material relates to the development of the medical center and the Eastern Virginia Medical School and Andrews' tenure on the city council from 1974 to 1997.
The collection is arranged into the following series: I. Personal Papers; II. Medical Papers; III. Medical Center Planning; IV. E.V.M.S; V. Community Service; VI. Norfolk City Government; VII. Newspaper Clippings; VIII. Binders and Published Materials; IX. Oversized, Photographs, and Miscellaneous Items.
Organization
Series I. Personal Papers.
This series includes 3 sub-series: A. Papers of Dr. C. J. Andrews; B. Children; C. Household. The series contains correspondence of Mason C. Andrews and other family members dating from 1949 to 1997. Sub-series A contains correspondence of Dr. C. J. Andrews dating from 1932 to 1944. Sub-series B includes correspondence and material relating to Andrews' two children. Sub-series C contains material regarding planning and design of a vacation home, and boat ownership.
Series II. Medical Papers.
This series includes 6 sub-series: A. Lectures; B. Medical Tower; C. Articles; D. Norfolk General Hospital; E. Medical Societies; F. Audio-Visual materials. This series contains correspondence, dating from 1949 to 1973, pertaining to Dr. Andrews medical practice. Sub-series A contains materials used in medical instruction. Sub-series B contains material, dated from 1957 to 1960, on the development and management of the Medical Tower building. Sub-series C contains medical articles on a variety of topics arranged alphabetically by topic. Sub-series D contains correspondence, reports, and other materials, dating from 1957 to 1967, pertaining to Dr. Andrews practice at Norfolk General Hospital. Sub-series E contains correspondence, meeting agendas, and other materials, dated 1950 to 1989, from various medical societies. Sub-series F contains two 16mm film reels and an audio cassette tape used in medical education.
Series III. Medical Center Planning.
This series includes correspondence, architectural drawings, reports and other materials dating from 1959 to 1973 regarding the planning and development of the Norfolk Medical Center complex.
Series IV. E.V.M.S.
This series includes two sub-series: A. Curriculum and B. Jones Institute. This series contains correspondence, pamphlets, reports, fundraising materials and the school's first yearbook. The materials included date from 1971 to 1995. Sub-series A includes reports and proposals for the school's medical curriculum. Sub-series B includes correspondence, reports, and other information on the Jones Institute for Reproductive Medicine and in-vitro fertilization.
Series V. Community Service.
This series includes 3 sub-series; A. Awards; B. Board of Directors; C. Sabine Andrews. Materials in this series date from 1961 to 1994, they include correspondence, reports, meeting minutes and agendas. Sub-series A includes mostly correspondence regarding various awards given to Dr. Andrews. Sub-series B includes correspondence, reports and other materials related to Dr. Andrews' service as director for various companies. Sub-series C includes information on the community service activities of Sabine Andrews.
Series VI. Norfolk City Government.
This series is divided into 10 sub-series: A. City Council Papers; B. Transportation; C. Cousteau Ocean Center; D. Nauticus; E. Waterside; F. Mac Arthur Center; G. Park Place; H. Commissions and Task Forces; I. Speeches; J. Mayor's Files. Materials in this series date from 1974 to 1997. Sub-series A, Box 19, includes mostly council meeting materials, minutes, agendas, and correspondence. Sub-series A, Boxes 20 through 23 consist of alphabetically arranged files each dealing with specific city issues. Sub-series B includes correspondence, and reports regarding the issue of local transportation. Sub-series C includes information on the proposed Cousteau Ocean Center that was never built. Sub-series D contains information on the development of the Nauticus project. Sub- series E contains correspondence and information on the Waterside Festival Marketplace project. Sub-series F contains information on the development of the Mac Arthur Center Mall in downtown Norfolk. Sub-series G includes correspondence, reports, and meeting materials related to the redevelopment of the Park Place neighborhood in Norfolk. Sub-series H contains reports produced by various city commissions and task forces. Sub-series I contains notes, transcripts, and correspondence regarding speeches given by Dr. Andrews. Sub-series J includes correspondence and other materials pertaining to Dr. Andrews' tenure as Mayor of Norfolk from 1992 to 1994.
Series VII. Newspaper Clippings.
This series includes clippings on various topics. The clippings are arranged alphabetically by topic and range in date from 1960 to 1996.
Series VIII. Binders and Published Materials.
This series includes materials in binders that are too large to be included in the other boxes. Boxes 34 through 36 are related to city government issues. The materials in Box 37 are related to Dr. Andrews' medical career.
Series IX. Oversize, Photographs, and Miscellaneous Items.
This series includes one oversize bound report, souvenir tee-shirt, seal, and photographs.
Contents List
- Personal Papers
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence Sabine to Mason N.D. (ca. 1949) (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Sabine to Mason 1949 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence Sabine to Mason (ca. 1949) (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence June-September 1949 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Personal Correspondence (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Personal Correspondence 1956-1986 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence 1992-1997 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Mrs. Jean Cooke Andrews (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Curriculum Vitae-Mason Andrews (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 9)
    - "Mason C. Andrews-the Dauntless Doctor" - Tidewater Virginia June 1983 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Postcards (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Cards (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Princeton Club (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Navy-Nato Contacts (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Presidential politics 1960's (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Drafts and notes Re: Biography of E. Stanley Jones and Howard Jones (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Postal Service-First Day Covers (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Sermon Re: Vietnamese Refugees (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Papers of Dr. C J Andrews
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1932, 1944 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with Senator Byrd Re: Children's Bureau Appropriation 1943-1944 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk Chamber of Commerce Correspondence 1940-1944 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk Association of Commerce, Statistics, minutes 1940-1944 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk Association of Commerce Slum Clearance Issue 1940 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence re William Cooke Andrews (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Children
    - Correspondence Re: Schools 1970-1973 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mary Mason McDonald Andrews (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Household
    - Mariner's Woods Subdivision (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Surgeon Creek (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Wetlands Development Permit Application (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Yatch-Shearwater (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Coastal Warning Facilities Chart (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Boat Gas Tax Refund (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 14)
- Medical Papers
  - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, John Hopkins Hospital 1949, 1970-1973 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Obstetrical and Gynecological Associates of Tidewater Profit Sharing Plan (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Assuring Learning with Self-Instructional Packages (workbook) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Medical Articles (Written by Andrews) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Epithelial changes in the puerperal fallopian tube by M.C. Andrews, includes notes and slides (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Clinical Research (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Ob/Gyn notes (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Minutes of business meeting Ob/Gyn deparment (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Medical instrument brochures (ca. 1950's-1970's) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Microsurgery conference materials 1977 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous 1977 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lectures
    - Tubal surgery lecture (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Incompetent cervix lecture (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Endometriosis 1985 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Notes for lectures (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Remarks for American Association of Gynecological Laparoscopists (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 5)
    - In-Vitro fertilization talk given to the Florida Obstetric and Gynecologic Society 1980 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Unicornuate Uteri (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Color slides: medical-Ob/Gyn (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Slide and lecture notes-Ob/Gyn (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Sodium Excretion notes (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Intramural pregnancy case study (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Medical Tower
    - Board of Directors (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Medical tower opening (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Emblem (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Kling, Vincent Architect (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence 1958-1960 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Articles
    - Arthritis and Rheumatism (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Aspirin risks in pregnancy (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Birthweight and diabetes (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cesarean section (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Clinical and legal implications of contraception (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Continuing education plan aids busy physicians-Richmond Times Dispatch Dec. 5, 1966 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Culdocentesis (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cytology (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Donated human ova (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Endometriosis (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Essentials of an approved internship 1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Extroversion of the ovaries (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Gynecologic Center (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Hippocratic Oath (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Home delivery (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Hospital management (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Immunization during pregnancy (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Incompetent cervix (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 18)
    - The infertile couple (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Maternal deaths from anesthesia and analgesia (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Maternal phenylketonuria (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Maternal Welfare and the Negro (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Menopause (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Obstetric analgesia and anasthesia (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Oral Contraceptives (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Ovarian tumors (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Ovulation failure (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Perinatology (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Premenstrual syndrome (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Preovulatory human ovarian follicles (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Posterior pituitary extract (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Prostaglandin (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Renal Tubercolosis (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Research in reproduction (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Sexuality (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Spontaneous abortion (role of genetics) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Statistical reports:infant mortality 1932 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Sterility (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Sterilization (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Surgery, annals, general information (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Syphilis (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Testis (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Thyroid Gland (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Toxemia of pregnancy (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Transplants (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Transverse presentation (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Trichomas vaginitis (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Trophoblastic disease (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Tubal ectopic pregnancy (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Tubal sterilization (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Tubal surgery (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Urethral calculi (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Urinary tract stones and infection (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Uterine hemorrhage (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Vomiting of pregnancy (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Weight changes and water balance in pregnancy (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 5)
    - What is a clinician and what does he do? (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 6)
    - X-ray pelvimetry (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Norolk General Hospital
    - Miscellaneous papers and correpondence (Box-folder Box 6, folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous papers and correpondence 1957 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous papers and correpondence 1958 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous papers and correpondence 1961-1967 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 11)
    - By-laws, rules and regulations (Box-folder Box 6, folder 12)
    - Committee and clinic assignments 1956-1964 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 13)
    - Department and committee reports 1963 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 14)
    - South wing addition 1962 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 15)
    - Resident and intern training programs 1958-1959 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 16)
    - Accreditation 1956-1958 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 17)
    - Disaster plans 1956-1957 (Box-folder Box 6, folder 18)
  - Medical Societies
    - American Association of Obstetrics-Gynecology (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 19)
    - American Association of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 20)
    - American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologistss (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 21)
    - American Fertility Society (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 22)
    - American Gynecological and Obstetrical Society (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Council on Resident Education in Obstetrics and Gynecology (CREOG) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Norfolk County Medical Society (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 2)
    - South Atlantic Association of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, correspondence and membership 1951-1973 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 3)
    - South Atlantic Association of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, meeting programs 1980-1989 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 4)
    - South Atlantic Association of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, programs 1970-1979 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 5)
    - South Atlantic Association of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, programs 1950-1969 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 6)
    - South Atlantic Association of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, papers presented to meeting, alphabetical by author A-G Feb. 1973 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Papers and case studies presented to the South Atlantic Association of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, Hot Springs, Va, alphabetical by author H-W 4-7 Feb. 1973 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Southern Gynecological and Obstetrical Society (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 9)
    - United Communities Council of Social Agencies-Health Forum (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Obstetrical and Gynecological Society Feb. 1973 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous programs of medical meetings Feb. 1973 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Audio-visual materials
    - 16mm film reel: "Normal Delivery" Dr. Barnes Film" (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 16mm film reel: "Pelvic Examination" (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Audio cassette: The Female Climacteric, vol. 1 #1 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 3)
- Medical Center Planning
  - Medical School Promotional speeches I (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Medical School Promotional speeches II 1959-1965 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence 1963 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Feb.-June 1964 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence July-August 1964 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Sept.-Oct. 1964 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Norfolk Area Medical Center Authority Nov.-Dec. 1964 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 1965 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1966 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 1967 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 1968 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 1969 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Jan.-June 1970 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence July-Dec. 1970 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence 1971 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence 1972 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Committee (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes/agendas (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Medical center testimony July 1965 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Medical community statistics (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Committee on education for health professions and occupations 1972 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Physicians for Virginia a preliminary report on a study of medical education (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Physicians for Virginia-a study of the feasibility of establishing a private medical school in the Tidewater area of Virginia" 1963 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Articles/brochures re: doctor shortage (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Academic manpower needs in obstetrics and gynecology (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Tidewater health foundation: statement of purpose, by-laws (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Legal agreements (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 11)
  - EVMS-brief of the Mayor's advisory committee on the establishment of a medical college (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Report: Medical School Status 1967 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Report of the first phase of a study of health manpower requirements (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk community health survey-preliminary outline survey guides Part I (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Brief of the Mayor's advisory committee on the establishment of a medical college in the tidewater area 1963 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Old Dominion College long range building needs part one: medical school affiliation (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Information and opinion relative to the proposed establishment of a school of medicine in Hampton Roads Virginia (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Architectural drawings and specs (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Norfolk medical center information booklet 1968 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Noback reports (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Application for regional medical program grant-project description 1968 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Virginia regional medical program (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Virgina regional medical program grant application (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Tidewater Rehabilitation Institute (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence planning commission Sept. 1957, May 1961 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Position paper:public health service hospital medical library (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Medical center plan May, 1973 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Basic steps in planning the nurse's residence and education facility by Louise O. Waagen 1953 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Info on other medical centers (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Healthcare manpower planning (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 7)
- E.V.M.S.
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School Campaign Oct. 25, 1972 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Virginia medical foundation endowment fund campaign 1984 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 4)